(Sheldon:)What about our trips
to Disneyland?
(Sheldon:)How can we do those things
with a child around?
(Leonard:)Relax, there's room
for two babies in this group.
(Sheldon:)Oh, dear L...
(Sheldon:)Penny's pregnant, too?
(Leonard:)You're the other baby.
(Sheldon:)Oh, really?
(Sheldon:)Okay, well, would a baby have
to shave once every 11 days?
(Leonard:)Would an adult refuse
to eat his graham crackers
(Leonard:)because one of them was broken?
(Sheldon:)I guess we'll call this a draw.
(Bernadette:)So, I'm glad
you guys are here.
(Bernadette:)There's something I want
to share with you.
(Bernadette:)Howie and I are going to...
(Penny(reading text):)Leonard says you're pregnant.
(Leonard:)What?
"Don't say anything.
(Penny:)Act surprised
when she tells you."
(Penny:)All right,
how you want to do this?
(Bernadette:)I'm pregnant.
(Penny:)Oh, my God, I
can't believe it!
This is so exciting!
(Bernadette:)Yeah, it's all real exciting.
Are-are you not
happy about this?
(Bernadette:)I am. Of-of course I am. I'm...
(Bernadette:)I'm sure it's just the hormones.